myactivitysheet.com 2018-04-09

# My Activity Sheet

* * *

MyActivitySheet.com ( ‘We’, ‘Us’ or ‘Our’ ) created the privacy policy ( ‘Policy’ ) understanding well your need for privacy and protection of any personal information that you may share with us , in an appropriate manner. 

By using our services (‘ Service ‘) which we provide to you through our website, MyActivitySheet.com and other products or tools , you signify your acceptance of this Policy. Policy may be updated or changes made from time to time. The continued use of our Service after such changes or updation shall constitute your consent to such changes. If you do not agree with this Policy please do not use the Service. Current or latest version of Policy can be viewed at http://www.MyActivitySheet.com/policy. 

At the time of registration to use the Service, for creating a user account, we request for your name and email address. You will also be asked to choose a unique password. We assure this will be used solely to provide access to your account. We do not trade, sell or rent users personal information. Your name and the email address may be used to keep you up dated about our new features, upgradation, newsletters, changes in the Policy or in terms of service. 

We will have access to the third party personal information provided by you during the use of the Service. The information, may include third party names, email addresses, their phone nos or may also have their addresses . This information will be used for servicing your requirements as expressed by you to Us for the use of the Service. We do not trade, sell, rent or share this third party personal information with anyone. 

Last updated on 3 February 2014
